postermywall.com 2013-11-29

# PosterMyWall | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Thanks for using http://www.postermywall.com/ (the "250 Mils Website"). At 250 Mils we are committed to protecting your privacy. We have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy. From time to time, we may update this privacy policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by emailing you and/or placing a notice on our Website. We encourage you to check back and review this privacy policy so that you always will know what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the 250 Mils Website will be subject to the then current privacy policy. 

### But first, a note about uploading and posting information on the 250 Mils Website:

At the time you register for a 250 Mils account, you will choose and provide us with a user name and password. When you upload a design, post a comment or message on the 250 Mils Website, your user name is visible to other users. Additionally, if your comment or message contains personal information and is posted by you in a page that is accessible to the public, third parties may make note of the information and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties as a result. Any content or information you upload is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Always use care when you post such information. 

### What information do we collect?

#### Information Provided by You:

You may provide us with certain personally identifiable information when you: 

  * register for a My250 Mils account;
  * order products or gift certificates;
  * request customer support or send us any other communication;
  * sign up for newsletters, email alerts, and special offers;
  * enter sweepstakes or contests;
  * sign up for, or redeem, special offers; 
  * respond to surveys; and
  * approve your child's request to open a My250 Mils' account in accordance with The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA).

Such information may include your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, and credit card number. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the 250 Mils Website or our promotions. 

#### Information Collected by Cookies:

250 Mils uses cookies on the 250 Mils Website. A cookie is a small text file on your computer which a website sends to your computer to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies our users. 250 Mils Website‚s cookies do not collect or store personally identifiable information. Rather, the cookie stores a token which uniquely identifies a particular user at a particular time. That token is then linked to the user information in our secured databases. You can always reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent. If you reset your browser, some of the 250 Mils Website features and functionality may not be available to you. 

#### Information Collected by Web Beacons and Log Files:

250 Mils collects certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of web beacons and log files. Such information may include your IP address, browser type, site usage, and whether you opened emails you received from us. 

### How do we secure your information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. The secure server software (SSL) we use encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your 250 Mils account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. 

We operate internationally and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States. As a result, your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with us, you agree to this privacy policy and you consent to the transfer of all information you provide to the United States. 

### How do we use information?

We use the personally identifiable information you provide to: 

  * provide the features and functionality of the 250 Mils Website;
  * fulfill your requests for our products and services;
  * communicate with you about the status of your orders and other inquiries about our products and services;
  * send you information about our products and services; and
  * provide notices about the results of sweepstakes, contest, and other promotions.

We use your email address to communicate with you about your account and to send you certain notification emails. You can change the frequency of those emails in your 250 Mils account settings. 

We use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send marketing messages and notifications from time-to-time. You may unsubscribe or change the frequency of email notifications on the Profile Settings page in "Edit Profile". 

If you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the 250 Mils Website or our promotions, we will use your friend's email to send them the e-mail you requested. Your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted. 

We use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the 250 Mils Website so that we can learn more about how people use the 250 Mils Website and improve our products and services. 

### Does 250 Mils disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

Generally, 250 Mils does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except that: 

250 Mils provides information to its agents and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes, such as: fulfilling customer orders and processing credit card transactions; offering certain products and services; communicating with customers; providing customer service; managing information on our behalf; and enhancing the 250 Mils Website features and functionality. In such cases, we require that these parties agree to use the information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our privacy policy. 

If you sign up for a promotion (e.g., a contest or sweepstakes offer) or enroll in a service we offer in partnership with a third party, we may provide information (such as your name, email address, and account activity) to such third parties. 

250 Mils may also release information (including your name, addresses, telephone number, and account activity) when we, in our sole discretion believe that such release is necessary or appropriate to: 

  * comply with law;
  * comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders, government investigations, or other legal process;
  * enforce or apply the terms of any of our user or license agreements;
  * investigate or respond to allegations of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity;
  * investigate fraud or similar claims; or
  * protect the rights, property or safety of the 250 Mils Website, our users, or others.

In the event that 250 Mils is acquired by, or merged with, another company 250 Mils reserves the right to transfer all information we have collected from our users in connection with such acquisition or merger. 

250 Mils may disclose non-personally-identifiable information to third parties in aggregate form to potential business partners and investors. 

### What about Children's Privacy?

Children under the age of 13 are allowed to upload graphics and images and to order products with their parent's consent. To order products, the child must indicate his or her age, submit his or her name and his or her mailing address and shipping address if different from the mailing address together with a valid credit card number 

This information is used to fulfill the requested order; confirm shipment; complete record keeping including royalty entitlements and pay royalty fees, if any, to report the sale of custom postage to the United States Postal Service, and to advise the child concerning new 250 Mils products, services or policies. 

Parents of children under the age of 13 have the option to consent to the collection of this information from their children or not. Such consent will not be used as consent for the dissemination of any of this information and the information will not be released by 250 Mils to third parties without the parents' consent except as may be required by law or upon court order. 

Personal information at 250 Mils is kept confidential and is disclosed only with the consent of the 250 Mils user or as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not engage in the selling of the habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our users. 250 Mils does not condition a child's participation in any on-line activity on the granting of any unnecessary information beyond that actually needed in connection with that activity. 

Parents can review any information 250 Mils has received from a child and the parent can have that information deleted and the parent can forbid the collection of additional information from their child. If you want to review any information obtained from your child or if you want to have any information obtained from your child deleted from the 250 Mils records or to forbid any use of such information, you may send a request to 250 Mils Customer Support by logging into www.postermywall.com, going to: 

Contact Us, and sending an email relating to Parental Notification. Alternatively, you may contact the 250 Mils Child Privacy Representative by email at: . 

### How can I change, delete, or update my information?

Most of your account information can be changed in the Edit Profile‚ section of the PosterMyWall.com Website. If you have any questions about what information is stored or would like to obtain a copy of such information, please contact us . After receiving proof of your identity, we will provide the information to you, and you may request that we delete or change any or all of the information. 

The current version of the 250 Mils Privacy Policy was adopted effective as of 05/18/2010. 

##### PosterMyWall Blog

###### Publicize your School Clubs with a poster!

Use our school poster templates to quickly make your club poster. (Apr 15)

###### New Basketball Sports Team Poster Templates are here!

Create your team poster in minutes by customizing an easy to use template. High quality prints and affordable downloads! (Apr 8)

##### Giveaways & Discounts

Connect with us to get updates and special promotion offers!

##### We'd love to hear from you!

Send us your questions or comments.

We need your permission to connect your Facebook profile with PosterMyWall. It will allow you to login to PosterMyWall using your Facebook account.

If you have any questions about our sign up process, please [contact us](http://www.postermywall.com/index.php/info/contactus).

### Please click the _Login using Facebook_ button to try again.
